<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourGuide</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">hello world</string>
    <string name="shanghai_description_1">The Oriental Pearl Radio &amp; TV Tower is a TV tower in Shanghai. Its location at the tip of Lujiazui in the Pudong New Area by the side of Huangpu River, opposite The Bund, makes it a distinct landmark in the area. Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="shanghai_description_2">Shanghai Disney Resort is a themed resort in Pudong, Shanghai, China. It is the first Disney park resort in mainland China and the second in China, after the Hong Kong Disneyland Resort. The resort opened to public on June 16, 2016. Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="shanghai_description_3">The Shanghai Tower is a 632-metre, 128-story megatall skyscraper in Lujiazui, Pudong, Shanghai. As of 2015, it is the world\'s tallest building, by height to highest usable floor. Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="beijing_description_1">The Forbidden City was the Chinese imperial palace from the Ming dynasty to the end of the Qing dynasty—the years 1420 to 1912. It is in the center of Beijing, China, and now houses the Palace Museum. Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="beijing_description_2">Badaling is the site of the most visited section of the Great Wall of China, approximately 80 kilometres northwest of urban Beijing city in Yanqing District, which is within the Beijing municipality. Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="xian_description_2">The Terracotta Army is a collection of terracotta sculptures depicting the armies of Qin Shi Huang, the first Emperor of China. Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="xian_description_1">The Reed Flute Cave, also known as the “the Palace of Natural Arts” is a landmark and tourist attraction in Guilin, Guangxi, China. Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="beijing_description_8">Beijing 798 Art Festival, as one of many an activity held in the zone, is celebrated at the end of every September. During the festival, professional curators are invited to make a thorough plan for the whole process, in order to display and highlight the charm and characteristics of the artistic zone, as well as to promote international artistic communication. The festival has effectively developed 798 Art Zone into a world-renowned cultural and creative industry district.</string>
    <string name="beijing_description_9">This interesting marathon integrates culture, sports, and travel. The area is famed for fine countryside scenery that you can enjoy as you run through fields and little villages. Climbing the 3,700 steps makes the course rigorous. It is now an international race attracting participants from dozens of countries.</string>
    <string name="shanghai_description_6">The Shanghai International Music Festival was founded in 2001 as a way to celebrate music in all of its forms in China\'s largest city. It was created when the Shanghai International Radio Music Festival and The Shanghai Spring International Music Festival merged.</string>
    <string name="xian_description_4">Phone: +86 29 8835 2698</string>
    <string name="xian_description_5">Phone: +86 29 8745 4678</string>
    <string name="activity_6">The annual Water Splashing Festival of the Dai ethnic minority falls during the New Year celebrations of the Dai Calendar. It is the most important festival observed by the Dai ethnic people of Xishuangbanna Prefecture, and, similar to neighboring Thailand\'s Songkran Festival, it involves three days of celebrations that include sincere, yet light-hearted religious rituals that invariably end in merrymaking, where everyone ends up getting splashed, sprayed or doused with water.</string>
    <string name="lhasa_description_6">The Shoton Festival is one of the most popular traditional festivals in Tibet. It celebrates eating yogurt, the Tibetan monks who end their season of meditation, the watching of Tibetan dramatic operas, and Tibetan Buddhism. It is held annually in the month of August, or late in the sixth month or early in the seventh month of the Tibetan calendar.</string>
    <string name="shanghai_L1">Pudong Xinqu, Shanghai Shi, China</string>
    <string name="shanghai_L2">Pudong Xinqu, Shanghai Shi, China</string>
    <string name="shanghai_L3">Pudong Xinqu, Shanghai Shi, China</string>
    <string name="beijing_L1">Dongcheng Qu, Beijing Shi, China</string>
    <string name="beijing_L2">Yanqing, China</string>
    <string name="xian_L2">Lintong, Xi\'an, Shaanxi, China</string>
    <string name="xian_L1">38 Huaqing Rd, Lintong Qu, Xian Shi, Shaanxi Sheng, China</string>
    <string name="beijing_L3">61 E 3rd Ring Rd Middle, ShuangJing, Chaoyang Qu, Beijing Shi, China, 100022</string>
    <string name="beijing_L4">9 Guanghua Rd, GuoMao, Chaoyang Qu, Beijing Shi, China, 100001</string>
    <string name="beijing_L5">67 Xiaojingchang Hutong, Dongcheng Qu, China, 100007</string>
    <string name="beijing_L6">74 Baochao Hutong, Dongcheng Qu, Beijing Shi, China, 100007</string>
    <string name="beijing_L7">28 Zhonglao Hutong, Dongcheng Qu, Beijing Shi, China, 100006</string>
    <string name="shanghai_L4">38 Gaoyou Rd, Xuhui Qu, China, 200000</string>
    <string name="shanghai_L5">803 Julu Rd, Jingan Qu, China, 200000</string>
    <string name="shanghai_description_4">Phone: +86 21 6433 5126</string>
    <string name="shanghai_description_5">Phone: +86 21 5404 5252</string>
    <string name="shanghai_L6">Shanghai</string>
    <string name="shanghai_date_1">Apr. 28 to May. 18</string>
    <string name="beijing_description_3">Phone: +86 10 5863 8203</string>
    <string name="beijing_description_4">Phone: +86 10 6587 2999</string>
    <string name="beijing_description_5">Phone: +86 10 8404 1430</string>
    <string name="beijing_description_6">Phone: +86 10 8405 0399</string>
    <string name="beijing_description_7">Phone: +86 136 9147 4408</string>
    <string name="beijing_L8">Beijing</string>
    <string name="beijing_date_1">the end of September</string>
    <string name="beijing_date_2">the 3rd Saturday of May</string>
    <string name="beijing_L9">Beijing</string>
    <string name="xian_description_3">Moon Hill is a hill with a natural arch through it a few kilometers outside Yangshuo in southern China\'s Guangxi autonomous region. Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="xian_L3">2 South St, Beilin, Xian Shi, Shaanxi Sheng, China, 710014</string>
    <string name="xian_L4">34 Keji Rd, GaoXin ShangQuan, Yanta Qu, Xian Shi, Shaanxi Sheng, China, 710075</string>
    <string name="xian_L5">63 Jiefang Rd, ZhongLou ShangQuan, Xincheng Qu, Xian Shi, Shaanxi</string>
    <string name="xian_description_6">The city of Xi\'an celebrates the New Year with bright, colourful lights at the Xi\'an City Wall Light Show. Since 1985, thousands of visitors have enjoyed the light-up figures of dragons, lanterns, animals and more creations. A family-friendly destination, there’s an area just for kids that has fun, interactive games. Performances include dancing and music entertainment from local artists. Visitors can also enjoy popular Chinese rice balls and other traditional food. Dates for the festival vary depending on the lunar calendar, but it usually begins in January, February or March.</string>
    <string name="xian_L6">Xi\'an City Wall, Xi\'an 710001, China</string>
    <string name="xian_date_1">January, February or March.</string>
    <string name="lhasa_description_1">The Potala Palace in Lhasa, Tibet Autonomous Region, China was the residence of the Dalai Lama until the 14th Dalai Lama fled to India during the 1959 Tibetan uprising. It is now a museum and World Heritage Site. Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="lhasa_L1">35 Beijing Middle Rd, Chengguan, Lasa Shi, Xizang Zizhiqu, China, 850000</string>
    <string name="lhasa_L2">Chengguan, Lhasa, Tibet, China, 850000</string>
    <string name="lhasa_description_2">The Jokhang, also known as the Qoikang Monastery, Jokang, Jokhang Temple, Jokhang Monastery and Zuglagkang, is a Buddhist temple in Barkhor Square in Lhasa, the capital city of Tibet. Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="lhasa_L3">Chengguan, Lhasa, Tibet, China, 850000</string>
    <string name="lhasa_description_3">Drepung Monastery, located at the foot of Mount Gephel, is one of the \"great three\" Gelukpa university monasteries of Tibet. The other two are Ganden and Sera. Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="lhasa_description_4">Phone: +86 138 8901 5053</string>
    <string name="lhasa_L4">No. 1 Danjielin Road, Lhasa 850000, China</string>
    <string name="lhasa_description_5">+86 891 632 8608</string>
    <string name="lhasa_L5">BaKuo Street Southeast DianXinJu Opposite, Lhasa, China</string>
    <string name="lhasa_date_1">Aug. 21</string>
    <string name="beijing">Beijing</string>
    <string name="lhasa">Lhasa</string>
    <string name="shanghai">Shanghai</string>
    <string name="xian">Xi\'an</string>
    <string name="beijing_1">Forbidden City</string>
    <string name="beijing_2">Great Wall of Badaling</string>
    <string name="beijing_3">Fratelli Fresh Restaurant</string>
    <string name="beijing_4">Ganges Indian Restaurant</string>
    <string name="beijing_5">Dali Courtyard</string>
    <string name="beijing_6">Mr. Shi\'s Dumplings</string>
    <string name="beijing_7">Black Sesame Kitchen</string>
    <string name="beijing_8">Beijing 798 Art Festival</string>
    <string name="beijing_9">Huangyaguan Great Wall Marathon</string>
    <string name="lhasa_1">Potala Palace</string>
    <string name="lhasa_2">Jokhang</string>
    <string name="lhasa_3">Drepung Monastery</string>
    <string name="lhasa_4">Tibetan Family Kitchen</string>
    <string name="lhasa_5">MaJi AMi</string>
    <string name="lhasa_6">Tibet Shoton Festival</string>
    <string name="lhasa_L6">Tibet</string>
    <string name="shanghai_1">Oriental Pearl Tower</string>
    <string name="shanghai_2">Shanghai Disney Resort</string>
    <string name="shanghai_3">Shanghai Tower</string>
    <string name="shanghai_4">Lost Heaven</string>
    <string name="shanghai_5">Shintori</string>
    <string name="shanghai_6">The Shanghai International Music Festival</string>
    <string name="xian_1">Huaqing Pool</string>
    <string name="xian_2">Terracotta Army</string>
    <string name="xian_3">Fortifications of Xi\'an</string>
    <string name="xian_4">Tongshengxiang</string>
    <string name="xian_5">Haidilao Hot Pot</string>
    <string name="xian_6">Xi\'an City Wall Light Show</string>
    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="date">Date</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
</resources>
